[{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980289300,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":28696,"timeElapsed":126888},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980298285,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":8982,"timeElapsed":135873},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980308324,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":10036,"timeElapsed":145912},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980315747,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":7421,"timeElapsed":153335},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980321822,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":6072,"timeElapsed":159410},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980326444,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":4620,"timeElapsed":164031},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980330900,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":4455,"timeElapsed":168488},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980345692,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":14788,"timeElapsed":183279},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980349423,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":3729,"timeElapsed":187010},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980360942,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":9808,"timeElapsed":198530},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980364752,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3807,"timeElapsed":202340},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980371280,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":6525,"timeElapsed":208868},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980373513,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":2232,"timeElapsed":211101},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980377286,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":3770,"timeElapsed":214873},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980380001,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":2714,"timeElapsed":217589},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980385287,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":5284,"timeElapsed":222875},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980389683,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":4394,"timeElapsed":227271},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980392388,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":2702,"timeElapsed":229976},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980406388,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":12956,"timeElapsed":243976},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980409670,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":3278,"timeElapsed":247258},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980412735,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3063,"timeElapsed":250323},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980416500,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3763,"timeElapsed":254088},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980420922,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":4419,"timeElapsed":258510},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980424285,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":3361,"timeElapsed":261872},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980430198,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":5911,"timeElapsed":267786},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980432846,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2647,"timeElapsed":270434},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980434592,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":1744,"timeElapsed":272180},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980444013,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":8220,"timeElapsed":281601},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980446418,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2403,"timeElapsed":284006},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980450396,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3975,"timeElapsed":287984},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980456204,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5806,"timeElapsed":293792},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980459379,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":3173,"timeElapsed":296967},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980463256,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":3875,"timeElapsed":300844},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980466112,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2854,"timeElapsed":303700},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980469194,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":3080,"timeElapsed":306782},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980472514,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":3317,"timeElapsed":310102},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980474552,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2036,"timeElapsed":312140},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980481488,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":5907,"timeElapsed":319076},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980483376,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1887,"timeElapsed":320964},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980490004,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":6625,"timeElapsed":327592},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980491878,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":1871,"timeElapsed":329466},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980494755,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":2875,"timeElapsed":332343},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980497586,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2829,"timeElapsed":335174},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980499764,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":2176,"timeElapsed":337352},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980517801,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":18035,"timeElapsed":355389},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980520797,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2994,"timeElapsed":358385},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980527150,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":5007,"timeElapsed":364738},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980528736,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":1584,"timeElapsed":366324},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980531126,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2388,"timeElapsed":368714},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980534255,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3127,"timeElapsed":371843},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980536846,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2589,"timeElapsed":374434},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980541516,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":4669,"timeElapsed":379104},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980543847,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2328,"timeElapsed":381435},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980546119,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2270,"timeElapsed":383707},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980548206,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2085,"timeElapsed":385794},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980554509,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":5048,"timeElapsed":392097},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980557541,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3029,"timeElapsed":395129},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980562916,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":5373,"timeElapsed":400504},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980564631,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":1712,"timeElapsed":402219},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980568170,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":3537,"timeElapsed":405758},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980575524,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":7353,"timeElapsed":413112},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980578142,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":2616,"timeElapsed":415730},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980585262,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":7117,"timeElapsed":422850},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980590873,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":5609,"timeElapsed":428461},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980600470,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":8606,"timeElapsed":438058},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980603634,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3162,"timeElapsed":441222},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980607002,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3366,"timeElapsed":444590},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980610392,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3387,"timeElapsed":447980},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980613289,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2895,"timeElapsed":450877},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980615166,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":1875,"timeElapsed":452754},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980616848,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":1679,"timeElapsed":454436},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980620970,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":4120,"timeElapsed":458558},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980622992,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2019,"timeElapsed":460580},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980631416,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":7039,"timeElapsed":469004},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980633157,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":1738,"timeElapsed":470745},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980641757,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":8597,"timeElapsed":479345},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980649560,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":7801,"timeElapsed":487148},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980654275,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":4712,"timeElapsed":491863},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980656156,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":1879,"timeElapsed":493743},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980658852,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2695,"timeElapsed":496440},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980665764,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":6910,"timeElapsed":503352},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980671329,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":5563,"timeElapsed":508917},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980673324,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":1993,"timeElapsed":510912},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980683726,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":9471,"timeElapsed":521314},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980685778,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2049,"timeElapsed":523366},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980689074,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":3294,"timeElapsed":526662},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980690542,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":1466,"timeElapsed":528130},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980694904,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":4360,"timeElapsed":532492},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980697794,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":2889,"timeElapsed":535382},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980701434,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":3638,"timeElapsed":539022},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980703899,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":2463,"timeElapsed":541487},{"subjectID":"x7h479bdtx","prolificID":"6717e7e21beb840c169fbcdf","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2316038b23bdc5095a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980706382,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2481,"timeElapsed":543970}]